Finding Aid for the Theodore Bikel Papers LSC.2321
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 1: Correspondence and subject files, 1946-2012
  - Subseries 1.1: Chronological files, 1946-2002
    - Fiddler box office, 1995 (Box 198, Folder 6)
    - Fiddler contract corresp, 1995 (Box 198, Folder 6)
    - Fiddler paycheck copies, 1995 (Box 198, Folder 6)
    - Fiddler schedules, 1995 (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - Fiddler P.R. and reviews, 1995 (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - Fiddler reviews, 1996 (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - Fiddler checks, 1996 (Box 199, Folder 2)
    - Fiddler contract, 1996 (Box 199, Folder 2)
    - Fiddler schedules, 1996 (Box 199, Folder 2)
    - Fiddler, 1995-1996 (Box 199, Folder 2)
    - Gen'l. corr., 1995-1996 (Box 199, Folder 3)
    - Fiddler corr + photos, 1994-1996 (Box 199, Folder 4)
    - Re: Sholom A. - FLA (Sholom Aleichem Lives), 1997 (Box 199, Folder 4)
    - Neil Jacobs, 1996 (Box 199, Folder 4)
    - SSP, 1995-1996 (Box 199, Folder 4)
    - Fiddler contract corr., 1996-1997 (Box 199, Folder 5)
    - Contracts completed, 1997 (Box 200, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence completed, 1997 (Box 200, Folder 2)
    - Contract correspondence, 1997 (Box 200, Folder 2)
    - Inquiries, 1997 (Box 200, Folder 2)
    - Metropolitan Talent, 1997 (Box 200, Folder 2)
    - Septee Project, 1997 (Box 200, Folder 2)
    - G, 1997 (Box 200, Folder 2)
    - Publicity + reviews, 1997 (Box 200, Folder 2)
    - P, 1997 (Box 200, Folder 3)
    - "Theo" the book Harper Collins, 1992-1995 (Box 200, Folder 3)
    - M, 1998 (Box 200, Folder 3)
    - Schedule, 1998 (Box 200, Folder 3)
    - Theo reviews later (accordion file), 1994-2002 (Box 200, Folder 5-6)
    - Theo reviews later (accordion file), 1994-2002 (Box 201, Folder 1)
  - Subseries 1.2: Loose and hanging files, 1962-2012
    This subseries consists of subject files that were loose, informally labeled, and/or not filed within Bikel's chronological sequences in Subseries 1.1. Most date from the 1990s-2000s.
    - AJC Symposium '62, 1962 (Box 226, Folder 4)
    - Soviet Jewry, 1964-1971 (Box 226, Folder 5-6)
    - Jewish Campus Youth report, 1968 (Box 224, Folder 4)
    - Schlussel - sale of 25 Bank Street, 1971 (Box 226, Folder 7)
    - Lubavitch, 1972 (Box 192, Folder 7)
    - ACA (Associated Councils of the Arts), 1973-1974 (Box 191, Folder 5, Box 192, Folder 1)
    - AFL/CIO general, 1974-1975 (Box 192, Folder 2)
    - DPE (Department for Professional Employees, AFL-CIO), 1978 (Box 191, Folder 3-4)
    - Theatre Communications Group, 1978 (Box 192, Folder 3)
    - (NEA), 1979 (Box 192, Folder 3)
    - Arts and older Americans, 1980 (Box 192, Folder 4)
    - (Bikel v. Reinhardt), 1984 (Box 226, Folder 8)
    - Home taping, 1985-1986 (Box 192, Folder 4)
    - History Los Angeles Project, 1988 (Box 226, Folder 9)
    - (Bikel - statement and eulogies), 1980s, undated (Box 226, Folder 10)
    - Questionnaire replies (FIA?), 1990-1991 (Box 226, Folder 11)
    - Holocaust Museum 4/22/93 DC, 1993 (Box 227, Folder 1)
    - The White House (ceremony to witness the signing of the Israel-Palestinian Agreement), 1993 (Box 227, Folder 1)
    - Pasadena, 1994 (Box 227, Folder 2)
    - Byxbe, 1994 (Box 225, Folder 3)
    - Publicity, 1999 (Box 224, Folder 7)
    - Gathering corr., 1999 (Box 227, Folder 3)
    - CG Playhouse, 1999 (Box 227, Folder 3)
    - "Theo" book contract, 1999 (Box 227, Folder 4)
    - 4 A's (accordion file), 1998-1999 (Box 227, Folder 5)
    - (Fiddler on the Roof - concert presentations), 1994, 2003 (Box 229, Folder 6)
    - (80th birthday), 2004 (Box 224, Folder 8, Box 225, Folder 1)
    - Bridge to Peace, 2005 (Box 227, Folder 6)
    - Serendipity 4, 2007 (Box 227, Folder 6)
    - (Rhode Island International Film Festival), 2014 (Box 229, Folder 7)
    - (Loose hanging file: AEA), 1960s-1973 (Box 194, Folder 1)
    - (Loose hanging file: "Hollywood"), 1959-1989 (Box 194, Folder 2)
    - (Loose hanging file: Newport Folk Festival/folk music)), 1960s-2012 (Box 194, Folder 2)
    - (Loose hanging files: Elektra Records), 1960s-1980s (Box 194, Folder 3-4)
    - (Loose hanging file: various political), 1960s-2012 (Box 194, Folder 5)
    - (Loose hanging file: Jewish music), 1960s-2000s (Box 195, Folder 1-2)
    - (Loose hanging file: Theo Jewish Theatre), 1964-2013 (Box 210, Folder 7-8)
      Includes material for Sholom Aleichem: Laughter Through Tears, 2009-2013
    - (Loose hanging file: Sound of Music), 1961-2009 (Box 232)
    - (Loose subject files), 1960s-2000s (Box 193)
    - (Loose subject file material), 1970s (Box 183, Folder 1)
    - (Loose material), 1970s (Box 192, Folder 5-6)
    - (Loose and hanging files), 1990s-2000s (Box 201, Folder 2-6, Box 202, Box 203, Box 204, Box 205, Box 206, Box 207, Box 208, Box 209, Box 210, Folder 1-2, Box 225, Folder 2)
      Files pertain to various performances, events, activism, and Bikel's autobiography. Box 208 and 209 have some hanging files with Fiddler on the Roof material.
    - (Loose subject file material), 1960s-2010s (Box 227, Folder 7-10, Box 228, Folder 1-3)
      Letter from Miriam Bikel (1981) in Box 227, folder 9.
    - (Address book), undated (Box 221, Folder 7)
    - Business cards, undated (Box 221, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 1.3: Actors' Equity Association subject files, 1960-1985
    This subseries contains a set of AEA files that was apparently retained separately -- see chronological files in subseries 1.1 for additional AEA files, filed alphabetically within each year.
    Files are arranged roughly chronological.
    - ACCA (Advisory Committee on Chorus Affairs), 1965-1967 (Box 166, Folder 1)
    - "Actors Drive for Equity", 1967 (Box 166, Folder 1)
    - Alien Committee, 1961-1968 (Box 166, Folder 1-2)
    - Constitutional Review Committee, 1968 (Box 166, Folder 3)
    - Council (misc.), 1960-1967 (Box 166, Folder 3-5)
    - Council - Special Committee on Structure of..., 1966-1967 (Box 166, Folder 5)
    - Council of AFL-CIO Unions, 1966-1967 (Box 167, Folder 1)
    - Dues, 1964-1967 (Box 167, Folder 1)
    - Elections, 1961-1967 (Box 167, Folder 2-3)
    - Electioneering, 1962-1964 (Box 167, Folder 3)
    - Ethnic minorities, 1962-1964 (Box 167, Folder 3)
    - General, 1968 (Box 167, Folder 4)
    - Gen'l. literature, circulars, 1960-1967 (Box 167, Folder 4)
    - Grievance Committee, 1961-1962 (Box 167, Folder 4)
    - House Affairs Committee, 1968 (Box 167, Folder 5)
    - Legislation - printed mat'l. re arts & humanities, 1963-1969 (Box 167, Folder 6)
    - Legislation - printed mat'l. re arts & humanities - misc., 1963-1969 (Box 168, Folder 1)
    - Legislation - printed mat'l. re Cultural Exchange Program, 1963-1968 (Box 168, Folder 2)
    - Legislation - printed mat'l re copyright laws, 1965 (Box 168, Folder 3)
    - Legislation - printed mat'l re immigration laws, 1965 (Box 168, Folder 3)
    - Legislation - printed mat'l re Kennedy Center, 1964-1965 (Box 168, Folder 3)
    - Legislation - printed mat'l re labor, 1959-1966 (Box 168, Folder 3)
    - Legislation - printed mat'l misc., 1961-1967 (Box 168, Folder 3)
    - Legislation - printed mat'l re taxes, 1962-1965 (Box 168, Folder 4)
    - Legislative Committee, 1961-1964 (Box 168, Folder 4-5)
    - Grievance Committee re Munso (reports, minutes, correspondence), 1961 (Box 168, Folder 5, Box 169, Box 170, Folder 1)
    - Hearings - Buchwald vs. Whitney, 1962 (Box 170, Folder 2)
    - Hearings - Feuer & Martin vs. Linda Johnson, 1964 (Box 170, Folder 2)
    - Hearings - Rich vs. Mercer, 1962-1964 (Box 170, Folder 2)
    - Hearings - Rogers vs. Scott, 1961 (Box 170, Folder 3)
    - Hearings - Bikel vs. Gregory, 1962 (Box 170, Folder 4-5)
    - Legislative Committee, 1965-1968 (Box 170, Folder 6, Box 171, Folder 1)
    - Lobby letters, 1968 (Box 171, Folder 2)
    - Lockout, 1960 (Box 171, Folder 2)
    - Minutes, 1968 (Box 171, Folder 3-6)
    - WCAB minutes, 1968 (Box 172, Folder 1)
    - (Pension funds reports), 1961-1970 (Box 172, Folder 2-4, Box 173)
    - Equity-League Pension Trust Fund reports, 1960s-1970s (Box 183, Folder 3-5, Box 184, Folder 4)
    - (Pension funds reports), 1961-1970 (Box 174, Folder 1-2)
    - Foundation for Extension & Development of American Professional Theatre, 1970-1972 (Box 174, Folder 3)
    - Hearings, 1962-1974 (Box 174, Folder 3)
    - Legislative Committee applications, 1969 (Box 174, Folder 4)
    - Membership Education Committee, 1969-1972 (Box 174, Folder 4)
    - Membership Relations Committee, 1969-1974 (Box 174, Folder 4)
    - Actors' Equity Foundation, 1970-1975 (Box 174, Folder 4)
    - Four A's (The Associated Actors and Artistes of America), 1970-1974 (Box 174, Folder 5)
    - "Any" Committee applications, 1970-1971 (Box 175, Folder 1)
    - Subscription television, 1969 (Box 175, Folder 1)
    - Election procedures, 1970-1976 (Box 175, Folder 1)
    - Constitutional Review, 1969-1971 (Box 175, Folder 2)
    - Budget, 1961-1970 (Box 175, Folder 3)
    - Contracts, 1964-1974 (Box 175, Folder 3)
    - Canadian Equity, 1961-1975 (Box 175, Folder 4)
    - Alien Committee applications, 1974 (Box 175, Folder 5)
    - Alien Committee - Working, 1967-1973 (Box 183, Folder 5)
    - British Equity, 1961-1979 (Box 176, Folder 1-2)
    - British-American Repertory Comp., 1978 (Box 176, Folder 2)
    - TV News Committee, 1962-1967 (Box 176, Folder 3)
    - Re: White Barn Theatre, 1952-1960 (Box 176, Folder 3)
    - Kennedy Theatre Memorial Comm., 1969-1971 (Box 176, Folder 4)
    - WCAB - misc., 1967 (Box 176, Folder 4)
    - AEA & SAG, 1969-1970 (Box 176, Folder 5)
    - Council - general, 1969 (Box 176, Folder 6)
    - General, 1970-1971 (Box 176, Folder 6, Box 177, Folder 1)
    - Alien Committee, 1970 (Box 177, Folder 1)
    - Nat'l. Conference, 1969 (Box 177, Folder 2)
    - AFL-CIO Demonstration Arts Project, 1967-1969 (Box 177, Folder 3)
    - Conference, 1970 (Box 177, Folder 3)
    - CRC (Constitutional Review Committee), 1970 (Box 177, Folder 4)
    - Elections, 1969-1970 (Box 177, Folder 5)
    - House Affairs, 1969-1970 (Box 177, Folder 5, Box 178, Folder 1)
    - Legislative Comm., 1969-1970 (Box 178, Folder 1-2)
    - Council minutes, 1969 (Box 178, Folder 3-5, Box 179, Folder 1)
    - Midwest Region, 1970 (Box 179, Folder 2)
    - Minutes - MAC (Midwest Advisory Committee), 1971 (Box 179, Folder 2)
    - WCAB minutes, 1969-1970 (Box 179, Folder 3-4)
    - Council minutes, 1970 (Box 179, Folder 5, Box 180, Folder 1-4)
    - Minutes - Council, 1971 (Box 180, Folder 5, Box 181, Folder 1-3)
    - Minutes - WCAB, 1971 (Box 181, Folder 4)
    - NLRB - Abba production, 1964-1965 (Box 181, Folder 5)
    - President's Planning Comm., 1969-1971 (Box 181, Folder 6)
    - Pension/ Welfare Trustees, 1970 (Box 182, Folder 1)
    - Pension-Welfare, 1971 (Box 182, Folder 2)
    - (Commingled Pension Trust Fund reports), 1971 (Box 182, Folder 3-4)
    - Mostel arbitration, 1963-1967 (Box 183, Folder 2)
    - (Loose memos, addendum, proposals), 1970s (Box 183, Folder 5-6)
    - Film, Recording, Pay-TV Comm., 1969-1976 (Box 184, Folder 1-2)
    - Nudity, 1969 (Box 184, Folder 3)
    - Council minutes, 1972 (Box 184, Folder 5-6, Box 185, Folder 1)
    - MAC minutes, 1972-1973 (Box 185, Folder 2)
    - WAB minutes, 1972-1973 (Box 185, Folder 2-3)
    - Off-Broadway negotiations, 1971 (Box 185, Folder 4)
    - Equity-League Pension/Welfare, 1963-1971 (Box 185, Folder 4)
    - President's Planning Comm., 1972-1973 (Box 185, Folder 4)
    - Pension-Welfare, 1972-1973 (Box 185, Folder 5-6)
    - Pension reports, 1971-1972 (Box 186, Folder 1-4)
    - SPACE (Scientific, Professional and Cultural Employees), 1973 (Box 186, Folder 5, Box 187, Folder 1-2)
    - Minutes - WAB, 1974 (Box 187, Folder 3)
    - General, 1974 (Box 187, Folder 3)
    - AFL/CIO SPACE, 1974 (Box 187, Folder 3)
    - Minutes - Council, 1974 (Box 187, Folder 4)
    - General, 1973 (Box 187, Folder 5)
    - Party for AEA officers, councillors & execs June 24, 1973 (Box 187, Folder 5)
    - General, 1972 (Box 188, Folder 1)
    - Casa Manana - Dallas, Tex., 1973 (Box 188, Folder 1)
    - Elections, 1973 (Box 188, Folder 1)
    - FIA (Federation Internationale des Acteurs) Stockholm, 1973 (Box 188, Folder 2-3)
    - FIA, 1973 (Box 188, Folder 3)
    - IFA Conferences (FIA) London/Paris, 1973 (Box 188, Folder 4)
    - FIA, 1972-1974 (Box 182, Folder 5-6)
    - Legislative Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 188, Folder 5)
    - Election (1973) congratulatory notes (Box 188, Folder 5)
    - Council minutes, 1973 (Box 189, Folder 1-3)
    - Election, 1976 (Box 189, Folder 4)
    - Names & phone #'s for officers, counselors, staff, 1975-1976 (Box 189, Folder 4)
    - General, 1979 (Box 189, Folder 4)
    - Los Angeles, 1979 (Box 189, Folder 5)
    - Personal, 1977 (Box 189, Folder 5)
    - NATR testimony, 1979 (Box 189, Folder 5)
    - Subregional, 1979 (Box 189, Folder 5)
    - TB testimony 4/18/78, 1978 (Box 189, Folder 5)
    - Personal, 1974-1977 (Box 189, Folder 5)
    - AEA Foundation, Emergency Fund Grant, undated (Box 189, Folder 5)
    - AFL-CIO "CPE", 1976-1977 (Box 189, Folder 6)
    - AFL/CIO CETA programs, 1975 (Box 189, Folder 6)
    - AFL/CIO Labor Studies, 1975 (Box 189, Folder 6)
    - Suppl. analysis Ruttenberg, 1978 (Box 190, Folder 1)
    - Pension & Welfare Trustees, 1977-1979 (Box 190, Folder 1)
    - Supporting materials reference, 1977-1978 (Box 190, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous/ pending, 1977-1978 (Box 190, Folder 1)
    - Minutes, 1977-1978 (Box 190, Folder 1)
    - Dick Moore & Assoc., 1976-1978 (Box 190, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1977 (Box 190, Folder 3)
    - MAB misc., 1978 (Box 190, Folder 3)
    - Legislative past testimony re NEA, 1970-1973 (Box 190, Folder 3)
    - Legislation labor law reform, 1977-1978 (Box 190, Folder 3)
    - Legislation civil service reform, 1978 (Box 190, Folder 3)
    - TCG, 1979 (Box 190, Folder 3)
    - Employment surveys, 1978 (Box 190, Folder 4)
    - Post-professional training, 1977-1978 (Box 190, Folder 4)
    - Press releases/ past file, 1977-1978 (Box 190, Folder 4)
    - Eddie Weston misc., 1978 (Box 190, Folder 4)
    - AE Foundation, 1977 (Box 190, Folder 4)
    - Four AA's matters, 1977-1978 (Box 190, Folder 4)
    - 1977 AFL-CIO Convention (Box 190, Folder 5)
    - Articles of interest, 1972-1978 (Box 190, Folder 5)
    - CRC, 1977-1983 (Box 190, Folder 5)
    - Energy, 1979 (Box 190, Folder 5)
    - 1979 AEA National Conference papers (Box 190, Folder 5)
    - Election 1978, 1976 (Box 190, Folder 5)
    - AEA/Fouratt, 1977 (Box 190, Folder 5)
    - Copyright legislation, 1978 (Box 191, Folder 1)
    - Stars Committee, 1973 (Box 191, Folder 2)
    - 1977 Nat'l. Conf. (Box 191, Folder 2)
    - Statistics (Arts), 1978 (Box 191, Folder 2)
    - 1985 Nat'l Conference (Box 191, Folder 2)
  - Subseries 1.4: Writings, circa 1960-1993, 2000s (Box 222, Box 228, Folder 4-7)
    Primarily drafts and research material for the publication Theo: An Autobiography (originally published by HarperCollins, 1994). See also Series 1.1 for subject files related to the autobiography. Subseries also contains research notes (box 228) presumably created for writings.
- Series 2: Musical arrangements, 1940s-2000s
  This series primarily consists of musical arrangements of Bikel's standard performance pieces along with lyrics, songbooks, album information, and publisher correspondence. Includes music from classical, musical theater, and Jewish, American, and Russian folk genres in English, German, Hebrew, Russian, Spanish, and Yiddish. This series also includes two 7-inch vinyl records and one audiocassette.
  Files maintain their existing order which was presumably kept by Bikel.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  CONTAINS UNPROCESSED AUDIO MATERIALS: Materials will require assessment and may need further processing for safe access. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
  - Fretts, 1961 (Box 239, Folder 1)
  - GR, 1968 (Box 239, Folder 2)
  - Mendocino Robin, 1961-1962 (Box 239, Folder 3)
  - Peggy Seeger, The five-string Banjo, 1960 (Box 239, Folder 4)
  - Performed song lyrics and booklets, undated (Box 239, Folder 5)
  - Rod McKuen, Brel Material, undated (Box 239, Folder 6)
  - Russian Folk Songs, undated (Box 239, Folder 7)
  - Russian Folk Song Books, 1949, 1966 (Box 239, Folder 8)
  - Sing Out!, 1966 (Box 239, Folder 9)
  - "We Are One", 1975 (Box 239, Folder 10)
  - "In My Own Lifetime", 2006 (Box 240, Folder 1)
  - Music for the Usual, undated (Box 240, Folder 2)
  - Old German TV Program, 1967 (Box 240, Folder 3)
  - "Tel Aviv", 1991 (Box 240, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Lyrics, undated (Box 240, Folder 5)
  - "Yiddish Suite", undated (Box 240, Folder 6)
  - "The Ballad of Cheatin' John", undated (Box 241, Folder 1)
    Includes one 7-inch vinyl record.
  - Folk Songs, undated (Box 241, Folder 2)
  - Folk Songs, Pop Songs, and Correspondences, undated (Box 241, Folder 3)
  - Folk Song Books, undated (Box 241, Folder 4)
  - "He Who Knows", undated (Box 241, Folder 5)
  - Leon Rosselson songs, undated (Box 241, Folder 6)
  - Leon Rosselson, Look Here songbook, 1968 (Box 241, Folder 7)
  - Manuscript Book, Handwritten Guitar Music, undated (Box 241, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Songs, undated (Box 241, Folder 9)
  - Popular Songs, undated (Box 241, Folder 10)
  - Prokofieff, Peter and the Wolf, undated (Box 241, Folder 11)
  - Published Film Songs, undated (Box 241, Folder 12)
  - Stage Music (songs), undated (Box 241, Folder 13)
  - "Amsterdam", undated (Box 242, Folder 1)
  - "Edelweiss", undated (Box 242, Folder 2)
  - "The First Time", undated (Box 242, Folder 3)
  - "In My Own Lifetime", undated (Box 242, Folder 4)
  - "Little Bit of Luck", undated (Box 242, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Parts, undated (Box 242, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Piano Conductor Scores, undated (Box 242, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Piano Parts, undated (Box 242, Folder 8)
  - "Moon Over Bourbon Street", undated (Box 242, Folder 9)
  - "New Israeli Song", undated (Box 242, Folder 10)
  - "September Song", undated (Box 242, Folder 11)
  - "Vieux Amants", undated (Box 242, Folder 12)
  - "Yiddish Suite", undated (Box 242, Folder 13)
  - Ed Sullivan Show, "Bikel Medley/Those Were the Days", 1968/9 (Box 243, Folder 1)
  - "The First Time", 1968, 1996 (Box 243, Folder 2)
  - "Man Into Egypt", undated (Box 243, Folder 3)
  - "Marieke," arranged by Fred Hellerman, undated (Box 243, Folder 4)
  - "Marieke" score, undated (Box 243, Folder 5)
  - "Marieke", undated (Box 243, Folder 6-8)
  - "A Pintale", undated (Box 244, Folder 1)
  - "Die Grine Kuzine", undated (Box 244, Folder 2)
  - "Kalt Wasser", undated (Box 244, Folder 3)
  - "Machateiniste", undated (Box 244, Folder 4)
  - "Machatonim", undated (Box 244, Folder 5)
  - "Moscow Nights", undated (Box 244, Folder 6)
  - "Am Israel Hai", 1998 (Box 245, Folder 1)
  - "The Bitter and the Sweet", undated (Box 245, Folder 2)
  - "The Fall of Man", undated (Box 245, Folder 3)
  - "Guajira", undated (Box 245, Folder 4)
  - "Haleluyah", undated (Box 246, Folder 1)
  - "I Am Free", undated (Box 246, Folder 2)
  - "If We Only Have Love", undated (Box 246, Folder 3)
  - "Shir Habokrim", undated (Box 246, Folder 4)
  - "We Are One", undated (Box 246, Folder 5)
  - Atlanta Symphony Setlist, 1980 (Box 247, Folder 1)
  - Atlanta Symphony Flute I Parts, 1980 (Box 247, Folder 2)
  - Atlanta Symphony Flute II Parts, 1980 (Box 247, Folder 3)
  - Atlanta Symphony Oboe Parts, 1980 (Box 247, Folder 4)
  - Atlanta Symphony English Horn Parts, 1980 (Box 247, Folder 5)
  - Atlanta Symphony Clarinet I Parts, 1980 (Box 247, Folder 6)
  - Atlanta Symphony Clarinet II Parts, 1980 (Box 247, Folder 7)
  - Atlanta Symphony Bassoon Parts, 1980 (Box 247, Folder 8)
  - Atlanta Symphony Bassoon II Parts, 1980 (Box 248, Folder 1)
  - Atlanta Symphony Violin I Parts, 1980 (Box 247, Folder 9)
  - Atlanta Symphony Violin II Parts, 1980 (Box 247, Folder 10)
  - Atlanta Symphony Viola Parts, 1980 (Box 247, Folder 11)
  - Atlanta Symphony Cello Parts, 1980 (Box 247, Folder 12)
  - Atlanta Symphony Bass Parts, 1980 (Box 247, Folder 13)
  - Atlanta Symphony Horn Parts, 1980 (Box 248, Folder 2)
  - Atlanta Symphony Trumpet Parts, 1980 (Box 248, Folder 3)
  - Atlanta Symphony Trombone Parts, 1980 (Box 248, Folder 4)
  - Atlanta Symphony Tuba Parts, 1980 (Box 248, Folder 5)
  - Atlanta Symphony Harp Parts, 1980 (Box 248, Folder 6)
  - Atlanta Symphony Timpani Parts, 1980 (Box 248, Folder 7)
  - Atlanta Symphony Accordion Parts, 1980 (Box 248, Folder 8)
  - Atlanta Symphony Percussion Parts, 1980 (Box 276, Folder 1)
  - Atlanta Symphony Guitar Parts, 1980 (Box 276, Folder 2)
  - Atlanta Symphony Mandolin Parts, 1980 (Box 276, Folder 3)
  - Bikel Bass Book, undated (Box 276, Folder 4)
  - "Shir Habokrim", undated (Box 276, Folder 5)
  - "Sunrise, Sunset", undated (Box 276, Folder 6)
  - "Tevye's Monologue and Rebuttal", undated (Box 276, Folder 7)
  - "Children's Crusade", undated (Box 249, Folder 1)
  - "From Volga to the Don", undated (Box 249, Folder 2)
  - "Mack the Knife", undated (Box 249, Folder 3)
  - "Amsterdam", undated (Box 250, Folder 1)
  - "In My Own Lifetime", undated (Box 250, Folder 2)
  - "The Megilla" and "In Droisen in a Regn", undated (Box 250, Folder 3)
  - "Shir Habokrim", undated (Box 250, Folder 4)
  - "A Chasene Tants", undated (Box 251, Folder 1)
  - "A Pintale", undated (Box 251, Folder 2)
  - "Aido Querida", undated (Box 251, Folder 3)
  - "Al Kol Eleh", undated (Box 251, Folder 4)
  - "Am Israel Hai", undated (Box 251, Folder 5)
  - "Anderleto", undated (Box 251, Folder 6)
  - "Arvoles", undated (Box 251, Folder 7)
  - "Avreml der Marvikher", undated (Box 251, Folder 8)
  - "Belz", undated (Box 251, Folder 9)
  - "Benjamin's Bar Mitzvah", undated (Box 251, Folder 10)
  - "Los Bilbilicos", undated (Box 251, Folder 11)
  - "Borukh Habo", undated (Box 251, Folder 12)
  - "Bosno Moja", undated (Box 251, Folder 13)
  - "Carlebach Medley", undated (Box 251, Folder 14)
  - "Chazan Oyf Shabbes", undated (Box 251, Folder 15)
  - "La Comida La Manana", undated (Box 251, Folder 16)
  - "Dudule", undated (Box 251, Folder 17)
  - "Edelweiss", undated (Box 251, Folder 18)
  - "Esa Enai", undated (Box 251, Folder 19)
  - "Es Brent", undated (Box 251, Folder 20)
  - "The First Time", undated (Box 251, Folder 21)
  - "I Am Free", undated (Box 251, Folder 22)
  - "Hulyet", undated (Box 251, Folder 23)
  - "Hamisha Asar", undated (Box 251, Folder 24)
  - "Hamish Assar/La Comida", undated (Box 251, Folder 25)
  - "Hanshamah Lakh", undated (Box 251, Folder 26)
  - "Hativka", undated (Box 251, Folder 27)
  - "Hey Klezmorim", undated (Box 251, Folder 28)
  - "If I Were a Rich Man", 2006 (Box 251, Folder 29)
  - "If We Only Have Love", 2006 (Box 251, Folder 30)
  - "Ir me quiero, madre", undated (Box 251, Folder 31)
  - "Jerusalem is Mine", undated (Box 251, Folder 32)
  - "Kinder Yoren", undated (Box 252, Folder 1)
  - "Kitaltas", undated (Box 252, Folder 2)
  - "Kum Aher, Du Filozof", undated (Box 252, Folder 3)
  - "Lekha Dodi", undated (Box 252, Folder 4)
  - "Leyg dayn Kop", undated (Box 252, Folder 5)
  - "Mack the Knife", 2006 (Box 252, Folder 6)
  - "Man Into Egypt", undated (Box 252, Folder 7)
  - "Mighty Day", undated (Box 252, Folder 8)
  - "Moj Dilbere", undated (Box 252, Folder 9)
  - "Moon Over Bourbon Street", undated (Box 252, Folder 10)
  - "Mot'l", undated (Box 252, Folder 11)
  - "Next Year", undated (Box 252, Folder 12)
  - "Nign", undated (Box 252, Folder 13)
  - "Niska Banja", undated (Box 252, Folder 14)
  - "Nye Bayussya", undated (Box 252, Folder 15)
  - "Oj Safet Sajo", undated (Box 252, Folder 16)
  - "Opening - Tradition", undated (Box 252, Folder 17)
  - "Osseh Shalom", undated (Box 252, Folder 18)
  - "Oyfn Pripetshik", undated (Box 252, Folder 19)